{
    "subject": "resource/Maverick_(film)",
    "predicate": "property/language",
    "object": "English",
    "human_readable": "The language of the film Maverick is English.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9580161571502686,
            "question": "Is English the primary language used in the movie Maverick?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8983420133590698,
            "question": "What language is the film Maverick spoken in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7226283550262451,
            "question": "Is English a significant part of Maverick's storytelling?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6988185048103333,
            "question": "What is the language of communication in Maverick?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6978353261947632,
            "question": "Is English essential for understanding the plot of Maverick?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6382001042366028,
            "question": "In what language was the dialogue recorded for Maverick?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5315812826156616,
            "question": "What language barrier might viewers encounter with Maverick?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4780980944633484,
            "question": "Could someone who doesn't speak English watch Maverick?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.42707714438438416,
            "question": "What is the primary mode of communication in the film Maverick?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.28333136439323425,
            "question": "Would a viewer need subtitles to understand Maverick?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The language of the film Maverick is English.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7661_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the primary mode of communication in the film Maverick?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7661_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Could someone who doesn't speak English watch Maverick?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7661_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What language barrier might viewers encounter with Maverick?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7661_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7661_130.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7661_131.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7661_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7661_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7661_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7661_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7661_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7661_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7661_82.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7661_90.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\"output\": \"yes\"}\n```\n\nThe document mentions \"Top Gun: Maverick\" and states, \"A very good movie in this genre is \u201cTop Gun : Maverick\u201d which can help improve your English.\" This implies that the language of the film \"Maverick\" (assuming it refers to \"Top Gun: Maverick\") is English."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}